1. Using a browser app, go to maps.Google.com

2. From the side menu, choose my contributions

3. Click on the photos tab

4. Scroll down to the very END of the listing - IMPORTANT. 
    Keep scrolling until the last photo is shown and won't scroll any more. 

5. Press and hold on a single word in a business title (NOT a photo) and choose 
    "Select all" from the pop up. The entire list of the photos should be highlighted.

6. Copy the text (or share the text if it's an option) to a TEXT ONLY file editor. 
    It is important that you save the text in a text only file and must be named with
    a ".txt" extension. Add the date in the file to keep the file name unique. 

7. From your browser, open up the web address:
    https://davecorr.github.io/XP/Calculate-Map-Views_b07W.html
    
8. Click on the "Load File" button and choose the .txt you created. 

9. You should see your data displayed. It will contain "NaN" the first time you 
    open a file. 

If you have problems, send me an email. Include screen shots if necessary.